<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>André de Moraes</title><link>https://amancioandre.github.io/landing-v2/</link><description>Recent content on André de Moraes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>amancioandre@gmail.com (André de Moraes)</managingEditor><webMaster>amancioandre@gmail.com (André de Moraes)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 17:38:37 -0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://amancioandre.github.io/landing-v2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Conda Environments</title><link>https://amancioandre.github.io/landing-v2/posts/2020-04-30-conda-environments/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 09:42:49 -0300</pubDate><author>amancioandre@gmail.com (André de Moraes)</author><guid>https://amancioandre.github.io/landing-v2/posts/2020-04-30-conda-environments/</guid><description>No more tears! If you are a user of conda packages, more precisely Jupyter Notebook, as I am, you should wory - a lot! - with your programming environment and your OS. Your environment is one of the barriers that prevent you from cloging your system with all sorts of packages and their - conflicting - versions. Lets be honest, you don&amp;rsquo;t want a crucial package being overwritten on your system do you?</description></item><item><title>Economy and Research must be Integrated</title><link>https://amancioandre.github.io/landing-v2/posts/2018-12-03-economy-and-research/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 18:45:18 -0300</pubDate><author>amancioandre@gmail.com (André de Moraes)</author><guid>https://amancioandre.github.io/landing-v2/posts/2018-12-03-economy-and-research/</guid><description>That was the headline from Valor&amp;rsquo;s article on tendencies from October, 2018, that struck me earlier this month and kept me thinking about the time I spent doing research for my master degree. Let me resume the Ediane Tiago’s article main points for you and hopefully we will start building up ground for how to tackle Brazilian politics on innovation.
1. Converging Forces Ediane Tiago states that Brazilian economy is going to face two converging forces: advances on digitization and on science, both interdependent but rather miscoordinated either by government or corporations.</description></item><item><title>A Journeyman</title><link>https://amancioandre.github.io/landing-v2/posts/2018-11-22-a-journeyman/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 17:38:37 -0300</pubDate><author>amancioandre@gmail.com (André de Moraes)</author><guid>https://amancioandre.github.io/landing-v2/posts/2018-11-22-a-journeyman/</guid><description>The term Hero&amp;rsquo;s Journey was first brought to us by the anthropologist Joseph Campbell on this book &amp;ldquo;The Hero with a Thousand Faces&amp;rdquo; which describes the fundamental narrative of the mono-myth that bases the histories of many historical myths, such as Buddha, Christ, Moses, etc.
Today it is also used to build modern narratives, with Luke Skywalker, William Wallace, Frodo Baggins and almost any hero you can think of. Although strongly debated within Psychological Schools, the concept is still very present and influential on our society, so much so that we can feel them deeply embedded into us.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://amancioandre.github.io/landing-v2/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 17:38:37 -0300</pubDate><author>amancioandre@gmail.com (André de Moraes)</author><guid>https://amancioandre.github.io/landing-v2/about/</guid><description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m André 👋!
I&amp;rsquo;m a Software Engineer, defender of teams, thinker then doer, visionary, drawer of funny specimens and advocate of change! I like to learn and I tend to think a great deal before acting, I am social and communicative. I wear laid back clothes, because why not, coding is like exercising: you got to feel relaxed. Hoody, glasses and bare feet is the way I roll. This way I&amp;rsquo;ve coded a little bit of everything, but I&amp;rsquo;ve been programming professionally for three years now, so finding a career path for myself and mentorship is a desire, a must.</description></item></channel></rss>